Well, friends.  Quick
video.  Today is
parcel day.  We have two
trial
Lord of
the Rings collectible booster packs and I purchased
some for Commander Masters.
So, I thought we'd take a look at
them.  But
first, let's
discover these great
collectible or trial
boosters.  By the way, this is the
only way
to get the
One Ring card without a
frame.  So they are
quite rare.
Let's see.  These are trial
collectible sets that
go with
commander decks.  So, let
's begin.  But I'm
starting to worry.    I do
n't know why.  Oh, Brad.
Brow.  I hope I'm
pronouncing it correctly.
Without frame.  And we have a
foil Meriadoc
Brandycup.  Good.
Not bad.  That is,
pretty good for a
free
sample.  And the
Oathbreaker King and
Gimli, the
Kill Counter.  Again,
not bad for a
free
collector's set,
but let's move on.
Here are some things I picked up
for Commander Masters.  This is
mainly for pre-
concerts.  As you can see, we
ordered this on MTG Mate.  I'll
probably put the prices
on the screen, because the
Australian
card market doesn't react
as quickly as the
American one for some reason.  You've probably
guessed what this
set is, because I was very
lucky and was able to
get "
Sliver Hive" for...I'll
put the price on the screen.
I'm sure it was
around 19
Australian
dollars.  And I just
picked up some shiny
cards specifically for the
Sliver deck.  Hmm,
I guess this one wasn't
for the Sliver deck.
I think I just
threw it in the trash because I was
taking a lot of cards.  But here it is
.  Of course, "The
First Sliver", "
The Legion of Slivers", "The
Guided Sliver".  This one is from the
premium
Sliver deck.
For some reason, it wasn't in the
Slivers main deck.  It seems
very good.  Depending
on whether I want to
be too toxic
or not.  We have "
Poison Sliver", "
Litterjar Reflection".
Obviously, it's really
good because you play
Sliver and get another
one.  I also
really liked this
map.  I saw that no
one was talking about her
.  "Protégé of Sakushima."
So, it's for six mana
, with "instant" and "
cascade".  And in fact
, it becomes a copy of what
you extracted
through the cascade.  So for
six mana you
get two
Slivers.  Hmm, they are
the same.  I think it
was a pretty good
purchase.  I can't
wait
to try this.  Uh, yeah
, that's what we're taking
for Slithers.  And
here we have things for you, you
probably already see, I made a
mistake here.  I
accidentally picked up a
bunch of cards that
were already in precon, but this is
, of course, for a
planeswalker deck.
So, I'm pretty
sure that Call the Gate
Watch and Deploy the Gate Watch
are both in, uh, both
in the
planeswalker deck.  But the
Contentious Plan is to
proliferate and
take the card.  So,
adding a
loyalty token to all
your planeswalkers
and taking a card
sounds good.
Naret, for some reason I
just
misread the list, and
she's already there.  Chandra's
Incinerator.  I really
like this map.    I
don't know if
she'll necessarily go
to planeswalkers, but
she works with Commodore Guff
, who deals damage to
all players, and that
will allow you to
deal double
damage.  If you're playing
all
Chandra planeswalkers, that of course
fits into the deck really well too.
So, I don't know.  Nice
little map.
I didn't have one.  I
just picked it up somewhere
for a dollar or something.
This is another card that
I thought wasn't in
the precon, but of course,
if you haven't seen it.
You can
tap your
planeswalkers to
untap Honor-Worn
Shaku and regain
colorless mana.  She will
go to another deck.
It's strange that no one is
talking about this map
.  The Peregrine Dynamo came
from the
Dominaria United Commander Sets.  All
planeswalkers are
legendary.  So you
can copy
their abilities
for just one mana.
Which seems pretty
good.  We're
going to
try this.
We'll see.
Teferi's talent, we managed to
get a very nice
foil copy.
Again,
it looks pretty
good.  You enchant
your planeswalker.
And for minus 12
loyalty, you
get the ability
to activate
the planeswalker abilities with Flash.  And
every time you
draw a card, you put a
token on the
enchanted
planeswalker.
Obviously,
we'll
add all of Teferi's
planeswalkers to the planeswalker deck
, which likes to
draw cards.  So, it
seems quite
achievable.  Of course, you
can't have a
planeswalker deck without
Luxor.  Again, I don't
know if this really
works, because you'll
mostly have
planeswalkers, and
turning them into
creatures makes them
more vulnerable to
removal.  Still, it
looks good.
Anyway, oh
my god, is she that
worn out?  I don't
know if the camera
captures that.  Oh yes, the camera
really captures it.    It looks
super scratched.
Maybe it's in a light
playable condition.  I don't
know.  Well, in
any case, "The Triumph of
Retribution" is a pretty
obvious addition.
Return all
artifacts, enchantments, and
planeswalkers from
your graveyard to the
battlefield.  Easy,
simple addition.  Uh
, Ikamun's gauntlet.
Again, the
Australian market is
slow, so I
got the foil one
for, I think, nine
Australian.
Again, it seems
pretty good.  Gives
all your
planeswalkers the
zero loyalty ability—
proliferation.  And for
minus 12 you get an
extra turn.  And
when you cast a
non-creature, choose
a counter on
target permanent
and put an
additional one on.  So, you
cast a
non-creature spell.
You get
single target
proliferation, which
again doesn't
look heavy in a
planeswalker deck.  And I
wanted to pick up
some interesting cards.
So I took Tehol,
Dominus, the blue
Dominus from "All Will Be One"
.  This is the complete edition.
Flight.  If you have to
proliferate,
proliferate twice.
Well, you can
make it
indestructible
by removing
the counters, which doesn't
look difficult either, but
here again you
can see
a lot of small
scratches on the card, which is
a bit annoying because I'm
sure I took it
as almost new.  Well, it
was these.  I don't even
remember what...I'll
make sure I don't
give away my address.    The
upcoming volume
will fix that.  OK.  What did
I take?  Wait.
I'll have to
take this off so as not to
reveal my
address.  Oh, yes, I can
actually tell you
about the prices I paid for them
.  Okay,
let's take a look.
So, I think it was...
I really
like how the
store made these
nice little
stickers.  So you
just draw
cards.  So we have a
lithoform engine
that we took
for just seven
Australian.  It
copies the activated
abilities of
planeswalkers, which
again seems
really good.  We have,
oh, yes.  We're talking about, oh
, what the hell is this?
Look at
the markings on them.  This
map is indeed
labeled as an "easy
playable state," but it's
quite disappointing.
Easy game condition.    It's like
someone literally
walked over it with a
pen or something
.
Anyway, we
got this one for 30
Australian.
I think it was 31. Uh,
Aurora.  This is for a deck of
spells.  An easy
way to send
spells to the cemetery.    The
Planeswalker deck is
Adoration,
obviously.  Uh, I don't know
what to call it.
It will probably be
Chandra.  Uh, we
got a foil
"Eye of Ugin" from the judge
, but again, is
that...I think I got
scammed, this is the first time
I've ordered from
these sites.  So this is the
judge's "Eye
of Ugin," and it had to
be in near
perfect condition.  But I
don't know if the camera
will catch it if...
Wait.  Let me take a
look.  Yes,
look, you see
it right where the eye is in the
center, right here.  All
these scratches.  Damn, this is
disappointing.  But
I think we got it
for about 30 bucks too.
34. Again, these are all
Australian prices.  Er
, "Moon Silver
Key."  I just really
wanted one because I don't
think...even though I made a
video about it, I have
n't bought it yet.  And I
like this one, uh,
with the black frame.  Uh,
KHN again.
Planeswalker deck.  I did
n't have one.  My God,
look at the
markings on this map
.  And it too had to be
in almost perfect
condition.  Okay, I'm 100%
sending a complaint to the
mail.  This is very bad.
Oh, that's really
disappointing.  "Rings of
Brightfire" is
back for the
Planeswalker deck.  Ugh, oh my god,
how she bent.  Oh,
that's very, very
disappointing.  I'm pretty
sure it
had to be in
perfect condition too.  Yes
, it should have been in almost
perfect condition.
Damn, we were just
thrown in with this hand
.  And the last card,
this is another card
I picked up for the
Eldrazi deck, "
Ruin Guide."  Uh, again
, the Australian
market is moving
slowly.  I managed to
snag it for two
bucks, I think.  Yes, $
2.60.  That's it.  These are my
purchases for the
Commander Master pre-orders.  Uh, there are a
bunch of other cards that I
couldn't get because they
simply weren't
available in
stores.  Uh, but
yeah, I'm actually really
upset right now
about the state of these cards.
So we'll see what happens
after I
send the letter.
Anyway, if
you want more
Commander Master content,
just let me know.
If there are any budget
deck breakdowns you
want me to do
for any of the decks,
let me know in
the comments below.
Thank you very much for
watching, and
see you
next time.